我要小鸡香溜肉片，不要康瓦尔烤鸡
I think I'll go with the chicken piccata instead of the Cornish game hen.
有素食选吗? 给我的?
Will there be a vegetarian option, you know, for me?
当然有了
Yes. Definitely.
是什么?
What is it?
跳舞
Dancing.
嘿 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我看到保时捷停在前门
I saw the Porsche parked out front.
你能把钥匙借给我一下吗? 我想带那个坏男孩去兜个风
Can I get the keys? Thought I'd take that bad boy for a spin.
罗斯可以开它? 我问你时你说只有你能开它
Ross drives it? When I ask, you say you're the only one allowed to drive it.
他是我哥哥，而且他开车那么慢，不会出事的
He's my brother, plus he drives so slow he could never hurt it.
它是辆车子，莫妮卡，不是火箭
It's a car, Monica, not a rocket ship.
兜完风后，帮我换一下刹车灯的灯泡
Just replace the bulbs in the brake lights after you're done.
嘿 嘿
- Hey. - Hi.
我看到保时提了，它真的很酷 我什么时候能再开着它去兜风?
Saw the Porsche. Looking good. When can I take it out again?
-你让乔伊开保时捷? -我从来没开过它，一次都没有
- You let Joey drive it? - I've never driven it. Not once.
好吧，只有一次 好吧，我常开着它出门
Okay, once. Okay, I drive it all the time.
我们的“你可以开它去兜风 但别告诉瑞秋”计划宣告失败
So much for the "you-can-drive-it but-don't-tell-Rachel" plan.
哇，我不敢相信你骗我
Wow, I can't believe you lied to me.
交给我来吧，莫妮卡 瑞秋认为你只会谈婚礼的事
I can fix this. Monica, Rachel thinks all you talk about is the wedding.
我说出你们俩的秘密，现在扯平了
There. I've blown both your secrets. Now we're even.
我不会让你开保时捷 因为你是个很差劲的司机
I won't let you drive the Porsche because you're a terrible driver.
好了，那跟婚礼的事无关
There. That wasn't about the wedding.
如果你想开保时捷去兜风 我可以载你在街角转一下
If you want a ride in the Porsche, I'll take you around the block.
要花好几个小时的时间吗?
You got a couple hours?
Friends S07E22 钱德的父亲
The One With Chandler's Dad
哦，真是痛快
Whew, that was a brisk ride.
-你开了篷吧? -跟飞上天差不多
- Take the top down, did you? - Only way to fly.
把钥匙给我，莫妮卡错了 我是个很棒的司机
Give me the keys. Monica's wrong. I'm an excellent driver.
你太快，又不负责任 你的确是个差劲的司机
You're fast and irresponsible.That adds up to a bad driver.
高中时 那些特点让我成为啦啦队长
In high school, that added up to head cheerleader.
你看到那个女孩看我的眼神了吗?
Did you see the look that girl just gave me?
她一定看到了我开保时捷的模样
She must've seen me cruising in the bad boy.
-她在看你的蜂窝头 -什么?
- She's checking out your beehive. - What?
-把梳子给我 -钥匙给我
- Give me a brush. - The keys.
-不行 -那我就不给你梳子
- No way! - Well, no brush.
好吧，那不重要
Fine. It doesn't matter.
如果我没记错 洗手间地上有一把梳子
If I remember correctly, there's a comb on the floor of the bathroom.
这是我的赡养费
Alimony.
你爸还没寄回函给我们
We still haven't gotten an RSVP from your dad.
哦，对，或许那是因为我没寄喜贴给他
Oh, right. Maybe that's because I didn't send him an invitation.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
喜贴? 这就好像叫他来参加了
An invitation? That's like almost asking him to come.
他是你爸爸，他应该来参加我们的婚礼
He's your father. He should be at our wedding.
本来我要给他寄喜贴的 当我看到邮票时
I was gonna send him an invite but then I saw the stamp.
那是玛丽莲・梦露的邮票，于是我想：
It was one of those Marilyn Monroe stamps and I thought:
我爸有那套衣服
My dad has that dress.
哇，他站在通风口那里一定别有一番风情
- Wow. - That must be a very different view when he stands over an air vent.
你会看到他签名“生日快乐，总统先生”
You should see him singing "Happy Birthday, Mr. President."
我们应该邀请他
We have to invite him.
我甚至不认得他 我好几年没跟他见过面
I don't even know the man. I haven't seen him in years.
如果他知道我们没有邀请他呢?
And when he finds out he wasn't asked?
我们的生活圈不一样
We don't run in the same circles.
我跟你们来往，而他…
I hang out with you guys and he...
他在拉斯维加斯表演变装秀
...stars in a drag show in Vegas.
我想和他交换生活圈
I think I want to trade circles.
你不会想邀请他来的 没有人会看新娘…
You don't want him there. Nobody will stare at the bride...
因为新郎的爸爸穿着露背装
...when the father of the groom is wearing a backless dress.
那又怎么样? 只要他不穿婚纱我根本不会在乎的
So what? As long as he's not wearing a white dress and veil, I don't care.
我想我得去买点东西
I think I need to do some shopping.
太棒了
Nice.
我的天啊!
My God!
-你以为你在做什么? -我只是在洗挡风玻璃
- What do you think you're doing? - Just washing the windshield.
我绝不会让你开这辆车
There's no way I'll let you drive this car.
-找不到梳子? -没有
- Couldrt find the comb? - No.
你为什么不把钥匙还给我?
Why don't you just hand over the keys.
喔!
Oh!
别启动引擎
Do not start this car.
好吧，我给你二十块…
Okay, okay. I will give you 20 bucks...
只要你立刻下车，嘿!
...if you get out of this car right now. Hey!
听着
Look.
如果你真的那么害怕，快上车吧
If you're so freaked out, just get in the car.
跟你一起去兜风? 对，是啊
With you? Yeah, right.
好吧
All right.
好吧…
Okay, okay, okay.
-你在做什么?坐到前面来 -你要我坐死亡之座?
- What are you doing? Get in the front. - In the death seat?!
-嘿，大家好 -嘿，甜心
- Hey, guys. - Hi, sweetie.
-准备要走了吗? -我的皮包在莫妮卡家，我马上回来
- Ready to go?- My purse is at Monica's. I'll be back.
-等一下 -什么? 喔
- Wait a minute. - What? Oh.
效果持久
That one kept going.
你跟菲比在交往?
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
-你们交往多久了? -一个多月
- How long have you been going out? - Over a month.
我们应该多我了解彼此
We ought to get to know each other better.
-当然，我很愿意-对，所以…
- Sure. I'd like that. - Yeah. So, uh...
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
-我是杰克 -我是乔伊
- It's Jake. - Joey.
-你喜欢尼克队吗? -当然，我是他们的头号球迷
- Do you like the Knicks? - Yeah, big fan.
我也是，星期二有比赛 你要一起去吗?
Me too. There's a game on Tuesday. Do you want to go?
太棒了，我得先确定星期二我没事
Great! Let me make sure I'm not doing anything Tuesday.
拿去吧
Here.
-这是什么? -你的行李 我们要去拉斯维加斯
- What's this? - Your suitcase. We're going to Vegas.
你是认真的吗? 我们要私奔？不必再筹备那个笨婚礼
Are you serious? Eloping? No more stupid wedding stuff.
不必再烦恼那些花 想想我们省了多少钱
No more these flowers, these flowers.Think of the money we'll save.
我们没有要私奔，我喜欢花 我们的婚礼能再盛大一点吗? 拜托
We're not eloping. I love the flowers. Can our wedding be bigger, please?
我们要去找你爸
We're going to see your dad.
我想认识我公公
I want to get to know my father-in-law.
我们已经谈过这件事，我赢了
We already went over this and I won.
不，你没赢，甜心，你应该知道…
No, you didn't. Honey, just so you know...
现在你要娶我，你是赢不了的
Now that you're marrying me, you don't get to win anymore.
算了吧，我不想去，我不想见到他
Forget it. I don't want to go. I don't want to see him.
我知道你爸让你觉得丢脸
I know your dad embarrassed you.
所有的孩子都会觉得自己的父母很丢脸
All kids are embarrassed by their parents.
你得想个新说法来形容我的经历
You'd have to come up with a new word for what I went through.
在高中的时候他参加了我所有的游泳比赛
In high school, he came to all my swim meets...
每次都打扮成不一样的好莱坞明星
...dressed as a different Hollywood starlet.
我十四岁的日子很不好过
It's hard enough to be 14.
我瘦巴巴的，穿着紧身泳裤 我妈还说有一天它会适合我
You're skinny, you're wearing Speedos that your mom promised you'd grow into.
我抬头看着看台，发现我爸在我为加油
You look up in the stands. There's your dad cheering you on.
他打扮成卡曼米兰达（性感女演员）戴着有真水果头饰的帽子
Dressed as Carmen Miranda, wearing a headdress with real fruit...
之后他会把那些水果交给你的朋友，作为饭后果
...that he will later hand out to your friends as a healthy snack.
他已经在那里了!
But he was there!
我爸爸不来参加我的核仁巧克力饼比赛
My dad didn't come to one of my Brownie meetings.
你是核仁巧克力饼?
You were a Brownie?
不是，我吃掉它们
No. I ate them.
重点是他参加了你每一场游泳比赛，帮你加油
The point is, he was at every one of your swim meets, cheering you on.
他是个好爸爸
That's a pretty great dad.
他跟嘉利巴迪先生上床
He had sex with Mr. Garibaldi.
-谁是嘉利巴迪先生? -那很重要吗?
- Who's Mr. Garibaldi? - Does it matter?!
你不再是十四岁的孩子 好吗? 或许你该忘了那些事
You're not 14 anymore, okay? Maybe it's time you let that stuff go.
如果他没来参加你的婚礼 你会遗憾终生的
If he's not at your wedding, you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
好吧，但我这么做是为了你
Okay, but I'm just doing this for you.
-我永远都赢不了吗? -你以前又赢过几次?
- So I never get to win anymore? - How much did you ever win before?
你知道当你穿着裤子身体往前倾时…
You know how when you're wearing pants and you lean forward...
我可以看到你的内裤吗?
...I check out your underwear?
哦，当杰克那么做时…
Well, when Jake did it...
我看到他穿着女人的内裤
...I saw that he was wearing women's underwear.
我知道，那是我的内裤
I know. They were mine.
噢!
Oh!
不，等一下，那太奇怪了
No, no, wait. That's weird.
我们只是闹着玩 我跟他打赌他不敢穿上它们
We were goofing around, and I dared him to try them on.
那真的很奇怪
That's weird!
-我正穿着他的内裤 -那真的 很性感
- I'm wearing his briefs right now. - That's kind of hot.
我也那么认为，你知道那个小洞吗? 它刚好可以放我的口红
I think so too. And that little flap? It's great for holding my lipstick.
我倒是不知道那一点
I wouldn't know about that.
杰克说，事实上女人的内裤更舒服
Jake says that womers underwear is actually more comfortable.
他喜欢丝质内裤贴在他皮肤上的感觉
He loves how silk feels against his skin.
接下来他会说 穿上你的高跟鞋他更婀娜多姿
Next he'll say your high heels are good for his posture.
杰克没有什么不正常的 他是个货真价实的男人
There's nothing wrong with Jake. He is all man.
我担心的是你
I think more than you.
他看起来像是穿着粉红色蕾丝内裤的伐木工人
He looked like a real lumberjack in those pink lacies.
我是说只有真正相信自己男子气概的男人．．
I'm just saying only a man completely secure in his masculinity...
才会穿上女人的内裤 我敢说你办不到
...could wear womers underwear. I don't think you could.
-我很相信我的男子气概 -好吧，随便你
- I am secure with my masculinity. - Okay, whatever.
你看过我收集的色情杂志了吧?
You've seen my huge stack of porn, right?
你的
Here you go.
随便你看，那儿什么也没有
Look all you want. There's nothing there.
慢点，否则我会坐回后座去
Slow down, or I am returning to the back seat.
冷静好吗?
Would you calm down?
不! 你超速15英里了
No! You're driving 15 miles over the speed limit.
我只超速5英里 他们只抓超10英里以上的
I'm driving 5 miles over the limit. They raised it by 10.
什么，他们疯了吗?!
What, are they crazy?!
天啊，我都忘了我有多爱开车了
God, I forgot how much I love driving.
我得去换新驾照
I have got to get my license renewed.
你的驾照过期了? 马上停车
You don't have a valid driver's license? Pull over right now.
罗斯，你太紧张了 你得放轻松，好吗?
Ross, you're so tense. You just gotta relax, okay?
你只需要放轻松，好吗? 放轻松
Just need to relax. All right? Just need to relax.
你再…? 那一点都不好笑，别闹了
What are you...? That's not funny. Stop horsing around.
我没有胡闹，好吗?
I am not horsing around, okay?
我在开保时捷兜风
I am "Porsche-ing" around.
喔
Uh-oh.
保持冷静，不会有事的 你没有惹上大麻烦
Stay calm. Nothing will happen. You're not in that much trouble.
真的吗? 你那么认为?
Really? You think so?
我是在跟自己说话，你死定了!
I was talking to myself. You're going down!
有人来帮你们点东西了吗?
Has someone taken your order?
对，她来过了，是他才对，是她吗?
Oh, yeah. She did. He did. She?
抱歉，我第一次来，我不…
I'm sorry, I'm new. I don't...
-我点了一杯啤酒 -你是异性恋，我懂了
- I just ordered a beer. - You're straight. I get it.
如果我们打电话给你爸 就能坐到比较好一点的位置
If we called your dad, we'd have better seats.
我不想让他知道我们来了 我还没有准备好
I don't want him to know we're here yet. I'm not ready for that.
而且他看到我也不会太高兴
Besides, he won't be too happy to see me either.
为什么?
Why not?
我不知道我有没有告诉你…
I don't know if I told you...
过去几年他常常试着跟我联络
...but he's kind of tried to contact me a lot the last few years.
什么?
What?
对，他会打电话，写信给我
Yeah. He's made phone calls, written letters.
他会到纽约来，但我总是说我很忙
He came to New York. But I always said I was too busy.
那就像是《摇篮里的猫》（哈里・查普林的名歌，讲述父子之间的问题） 我真的不想谈
It's very "Cats in the Cradle." I don't want to get into it.
节日要开始了
Here we go.
各位先生女士，欢迎与世无双的…
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome the incomparable...
海莲娜汉德巴斯奇
...Helena Handbasket.
嗨，亲爱的
Hello, darlings.
他就是我爸
And there's Daddy.
快跟我换位置，快点! 我在上面，你在下面
Switch places with me. Come on! I'll go under, you go over.
-对，我愿意那么做 -快点
- Yeah, I'll get right on that. - Come on!
-什么? 不，瑞秋，别那样 -快点
- What? No. Hey, Rach, come on. - Come on!
我相信我们不会因为这个而被逮捅
I'm sure we won't get arrested for this.
天啊!
God!
嗨，警官，我的速度有点快吗?
Hi, officer. Was I going a little too fast?
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
-麻烦你把驾照拿出来 -没问题
- Can I see your license, please? - Absolutely.
这太奇怪了，我昨晚做了一个梦 梦到我被一个警察拦下来
It's weird. I had a dream last night that I was stopped by a policeman.
然后他…
And then he...
或许我不该告诉你接下来的情节
Well, I probably shouldn't tell you the rest.
他给了你一张…
He gave you a big...
大
...fat...
罚单?
...ticket?
- 你的驾照 - 对，在这里，警官…
- Your license. - Yes. Here you go, Officer...
帅哥警官
...Handsome.
-是韩森 -对不起，我错了
- It's Hanson. - Oops, sorry. My mistake.
亲爱的主啊!
Dear Lord!
-哇! -来了
- Wow! - Here it comes.
这张照片很漂亮
This is a great picture.
真的吗? 你真的那么想 拍照时我才刚刚起床
Really? You think so? You know, I had just rolled right out of bed.
你看起来很美
You look phenomenal.
一点都没错，那是十年前的照片了
She should! It was taken 10 years ago!
你知道的，或许你很纳闷日期有点不太对劲
You know, you're probably wondering about the old date.
没错，你是水瓶座吗?
Yes, I am. You're an Aquarius, huh?
-我敢说你是双子座 -不是
- I'll bet you're a Gemini. - No.
-金牛座? -不是
- Taurus? - No.
-处女座 -不是
- Virgo? - No.
-射手座? -对
- Sagittarius? - Yep.
我就知道
I knew it. I knew it!
-不要再超速了，好吗? -我不会超速的
- You won't speed anymore, right? - I won't speed.
-你发誓你会去换驾照? -我发誓
- And you promise to take care of this? - I promise.
还有，让他开车，他有驾照吗?
In the meantime, let him drive. Does he have a license?
-他会开手动的车吗? -哦…
- Can he handle a stick? - Well...
我会开手动的车!
I can handle a stick!
-他不可能是你爸 -多年来我一直是那么告诉自己
- That can't be your father. - I've been saying that for years.
-哦，我的天啊 -什么?
- Oh, my God! - What?
弹钢琴的人就是嘉利巴迪先生
That's Mr. Garibaldi playing the piano.
嗨，欢迎你们来看表演
Hello, and welcome to the show.
在观众席中我看到一些常客
I see some of our regulars in the audience.
还有一些新面孔
And a couple of irregulars.
-他要走进观众席里了 -放轻松，你会没事的
- He's coming into the audience. - Relax. You'll be fine.
哦，好多了，现在你成了隐形人
Oh, much better. You're invisible now.
-你是从哪里来的? -贝克斯菲尔德
- Where are you from? - Bakersfield.
-什么? -贝克斯菲尔德
- I'm sorry? - Bakersfield.
不，我听到了，我只是觉得很遗憾
No, no, I heard. I'm just sorry.
我无法接受这种事情 我们回饭店碰面
It can't happen like this. I'll meet you back at the hotel.
大家看，已经有人站起来鼓掌 节日才刚刚开始
Look, a standing ovation already. So early in the show.
转身吧，亲爱的，让我看看你帅气的脸
Turn around, darling. Let me see your pretty face.
我们的饮料能快点送上来吗？ 服务生? 小姐?
Can we have our drinks, please? Waiter? ...tress?
-嘿，菲比 -嘿
- Hey, Pheebs. - Hey.
你看
Check it out.
我很有男子气概吧?
How much of a man am I?
哇，太棒了，你很有男子气概 但你也是个荡妇
Wow, nice. Manly, and also kind of a slut.
我开始了解杰克的意思了
I'm beginning to see what Jake was talking about.
丝绸的感觉真的很舒服
The silk feels really good.
而那玩意不像我想象中会挤在一团
And things aren't as smashed down as I thought they would be.
那真的是太棒了
That's great.
而男人的内裤选择没那么多
You have so many more choices than with mens underwear.
比基尼，法式剪裁，丁字裤，质料有棉的，丝绸的和蕾丝的
Bikini, French cut, thong. And the fabrics: Cotton, silk, lace.
你知道我一直想穿什么吗? 裤袜!
You know what I've always wondered about? Pantyhose!
从脚趾头开始一路住上拉到…
The way they start at your toe, then they go all the way up to...
-我应该把内裤脱下来的，对吧？ -我想你最好那么做
- I should go take these off, shouldn't I ? - I think it's important you do.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
钱德
Chandler.
钱德?
Chandler?
那个名字真是与众不同
What an unusual name.
你的父母一定很棒
You must have had terribly fascinating parents.
哦，他们只会大喊大叫的
Oh, they're a hoot.
你的朋友叫什么名字?
And who is your friend?
我是莫妮卡
I'm Monica.
-莫妮卡，你们从哪里来的? -纽约
- Monica. Where are you from? - New York.
我不太喜欢纽约
I'm not very fond of New York.
但我喜欢皇后区
Queens, I like.
这个亮晶晶的…
What is this...
东西是什么? 甜心
...sparkling something, honey, huh?
事实上莫妮卡跟我订婚了
Actually, Monica and I are engaged.
真的吗?
Really?
恭喜你们
Congratulations.
你们什么时候结婚?
When's the big day?
两星期后
In two weeks.
我知道了
I see.
喔，我祝你们两个永远幸福
Well, I wish you both a lifetime of happiness.
原来你是个秃头
So, you're bald.
等一下
Wait, wait.
我们希望你能来参加我们的婚礼
We'd love it if you could be there.
真的吗?
Really?
我知道那会让我觉得很快乐…
I know it would make me happy...
夫人
...ma'am.
我一定会去的
Then I wouldn't miss it for the world.
我都热泪盈眶了
I'm getting all misty here.
你们一定会以为是我刚用热蜡除过腿毛的原因
You'd think I was having my legs waxed or something.
-你还好吗? -我很好
- You okay? - Yeah.
谢谢你逼我这么做
Thanks for making me do this.
在继续表演前，我要跟这对新人说…
Before we go on with the show, I want to say to the bride and groom...
他们非常幸运能找到彼此
...how lucky they are to have found each other.
每个人的人生都会遇到雨天
In every life a little rain must fall.
幸好…
Fortunately...
在我的人生中…
...in my life...
我小时候演过最左边那个角色
When I was growing up, I played the one on the far left.
今天你一定玩得够尽兴的
I think you've had enough fun for today.
提醒我介绍你给某人认识
Remind me to introduce you to someone.
-谁? -四档
- Who? - Fourth gear.
他想做什么? 我什么都没做
What does he want? I wasn't doing anything.
或许他看到你的手只会从十点的位置滑到两点的位置
Maybe he saw your hands slip briefly from the 10 and 2:00 position.
或许是射手座警官折回来想泡你
Maybe it's Sergeant Sagittarius coming back to flirt some more.
也许他的警徽还没丢够脸吧
Perhaps he didn't tarnish the badge enough.
不是刚刚那个警官
It's a different guy.
-晚安，警官 -你知道你的时速有多快吗?
- Good evening, officer. - Do you know how fast you were going?
不，我不知道，但应该没有超过六十哩
No, I don't, but it couldn't have been more than 60.
你说的对，只有二十七哩
You're right. It was 37.
真的?
Really?
-请出示你的驾照好吗? -开玩笑
- Can I see your license, please? - You're kidding.
你该不会因为我开得太慢而开我罚单吧?
You're not gonna give me a ticket for driving too slow, are you?
没错
That's right.
你要帮我吗?
You wanna help me out here?
对不起，什么?
I'm sorry, what?
做你刚才做的把戏?
Can you do your little thing that you did before?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
我不能让他的警徽丢脸
I don't think I want to tarnish his badge.
你知道的，警官…
You know, officer...
昨晚我做了一个非常奇怪的梦
I had the weirdest dream last night.
哇，我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
麻烦你把驾照拿出来
Your license, please.
你不想想听听我做了什么梦吗…
You don't want to hear about my dream...
警官…
...Officer...
…可爱吗?
...Pretty?
是佩提
It's Petty.
我马上帮你开罚单
I'll be right back with your ticket.
-你有个儿子 -我知道
- You have a son. - I know. I know.
-你觉得好一点了吗? -对，我好多了
- You feel better? - Yeah. Much.
听着…
Listen...
我并不是担心我的男子气概…
Not that I'm insecure about my manood or anything...
但我想我应该马上去泡个女人
...but I think I need to hook up with a woman right now.
我了解
I understand.
你看起来好眼熟，我认识你吗?
You look familiar. Do I know you?
应该不认识
I don't think so.
或许那因为我是电视演员
Maybe it's because I'm on television.
-我演出《我们的日子》-哇，真的吗?
- I'm an actor on Days of our Lives. - Wow. Really?
-一共是四块半，谢谢，-让我来吧
- $4.50, please. - Oh, let me get this.
这是送你的
These are for you.